[instrumental music]
- Hey, Pheebs?
- Huh?
I'm having dinner
with my dad tomorrow night.
Do you wanna come?
Sure, yeah.
He's kind of sexy.
Oh, no.
No, I'll be there too.
Okay. So, we'll just come up
with some kind of signal.
If it's going well,
you can take off.
No, Pheeb, I just
need you there for support.
I haven't told him
that I'm pregnant yet.
Oh. Why not?
Because I know
he's gonna flip out
and I hate it
when he gets angry.
Oh, Rachel, this is all
so "Papa Don't Preach."
What? Pheeb, wait.
He's a scary guy.
I mean, one time
he caught me smoking
he said if he ever saw me
doing that again
he would make me eat
the entire pack.
- Wow. Well, I will be there.
- Okay.
Gosh, I'm not gonna let that man
make you eat your baby.
Oh, hey, who is that guy?
I think I know him.
- No, you don't.
Oh, my God!
Monica, he's the stripper
from your bachelorette party!
Her what?
Your secret bachelorette party.
You had a bachelorette party?
She untied his G-string
with her teeth.
[chuckles]
Somebody stop me!
I thought we weren't gonna have
bachelor-bachelorette parties.
You know, we-we agreed
that it was a silly tradition.
It's a grand tradition.
I'm sorry.
They surprised me.
There was nothing I could do.
Well, you could have
untied it with your hands.
Oh, for..
This is so unfair.
The one thing I wanted to do
was throw my best friend
a bachelor party,
but, oh, I wasn't allowed to.
All I got was
a stupid steak dinner.
You went home with the waitress.
Oh, yeah,
that was a pretty good night.
I can't believe
you didn't tell me.
You know that
the two pillars of marriage
are openness and honesty.
Oh, I knew giving you that book
was gonna come back
and bite me in the ass.
[theme song]
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's DOA ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been your day ♪
♪ Your week your month
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me too ♪♪
[instrumental music]
How about I order everyone
the Moroccan chicken?
Oh, I-I don't eat meat.
It's chicken.
Yeah, I don't eat that, either.
I'll never understand
you lesbians.
So, baby, tell me,
what is new with you?
- Well, actually, um..
- 'Ahem.'
Your '74 Lafite, sir.
'74? I ordered the '75.
That's a magnificent wine.
The '74 is sewage.
Why would you bring me sewage?
Is that a hard question?
Are you an idiot?
Is that why you're a waiter?
This is why I told the manager
I wouldn't wait on you tonight.
Oh, come on!
Don't be such a baby.
[clears throat]
In case you didn't notice,
that is a scary man.
He's right, though.
The '74 is absolute piss.
This was such a huge mistake.
I can't tell him, Phoebe.
- I can't, I can't, I can't--
- Rachel--
No, it's okay.
This is what's gonna happen.
I'm gonna wait
a couple of years
and then the baby
will tell him.
Why, so he can get mad
at the baby?
Hey, that is
the...baby's problem.
Oh, everything okay
with the waiter?
I have no idea.
I went to the bathroom.
So, sweetie, you were starting
to tell me what is, uh
what is new with you.
Well..
I'm..
I got TiVo.
- What's TiVo?
- It's slang for pregnant.
Phoebe!
Are you really pregnant?
Well, uh, yes and no.
Except not no.
So, to sum it up, yeah.
Who is the father?
Oh, no. Please don't
tell me it's her.
No, it's Ross.
It's Ross. You like Ross.
Oh, daddy, I hope
you're okay with all this.
I mean, think about it.
This is a good thing.
You're gonna..
This is your first grandchild.
You're gonna be a poppy.
- That's true.
- Yeah.
A poppy.
- I'm gonna be a poppy!
- Oh..
[all laughing]
Oh! So, when is the wedding?
Uh, hmm, the who?
The wedding.
There's going to be a wedding.
Young lady, don't you
sit there and tell me
that my first grandchild
is gonna be a bastard.
Rachel Karen Green, tell me
there's gonna be a wedding!
February 2nd.
[instrumental music]
So, it was really cool
seeing you lecture today.
Oh, thanks.
Although, uh, you kinda seemed
like you were falling asleep
there a little.
Oh, no, no, I-I had my eyes
closed so I could concentrate
and, you know, take it all in.
Yeah, a lot
of my students do that.
Mmm.
So, um, I gotta get going.
Okay, I-I'll see you tonight?
- Yeah. Okay.
- Okay. Bye.
Oh, hey, thanks again
for showing me
your semiprecious
stone collection.
It was amazing.
My God! You must be good in bed.
So, you and Mona?
It's been a while now.
How's it goin'?
Uh, it's good.
It's going, it's going good.
I mean, we-we get along great.
- She's, she's so..
- Hot?
Well, I-I was gonna say sweet,
but yeah-huh.
And she's okay with Rachel
and the baby?
Well, I haven't
actually told her yet.
I-I don't wanna scare her off,
you know?
Well, you have
to be honest with her.
Otherwise you may think that
you're going down the same path
but you're really
going down different ones.
I'm gonna take that book
and I'm gonna beat you
to death with it.
Oh, my God! You are gonna
love me so much.
I felt really bad about the
whole bachelorette party thing
so tonight you're gonna
have a bachelor party.
- What?
- Yeah.
I got this number
from this guy at work
and I hired a stripper
to come dance for you.
[chuckles]
Am I going in the
Wife Hall of Fame or what?
[chuckles]
Honey, that's crazy. I don't
want you to get me a stripper.
Will you let the lady talk?
Come on.
Come on, it'll be fun.
It'll make me feel
so much better.
[scoffs]
Look, I appreciate it
but, uh..
...it's a little creepy,
you know?
I'm not a bachelor anymore.
So don't think of it
as a bachelor party.
Th-think of it as a
a two-month anniversary present.
Sure. One year is paper,
but two months is lap dance.
Please. I feel so bad.
Just watch
the hot woman get naked.
Alright, fine.
But I'm only doing this for you.
Yeah!
And Joey.
Thank you. Alright. Now,
who else do you wanna invite?
Uh, no, no, no, just, uh, Ross..
Ross and Joey
is embarrassing enough.
Uh, actually, sorry,
I-I can't even make it.
- I'm seeing Mona again tonight.
- I understand.
I mean, who would cancel
an actual date
just to go
to a fake bachelor party.
I'm sorry, I gotta cancel
tonight, baby.
I'm sorry I won't
be able to make it to your
imaginary wedding, but I'm-I'm
really busy that day.
I-I already
have a unicorn baptism
and a leprechaun bar mitzvah.
I know, I know.
I panicked. I panicked.
I didn't want him to start
yelling at me like I was some..
...'74 Latour.
It's Lafite.
The '74 Latour is actually
drinking quite nicely.
Alright, here he comes.
I'm gonna do this.
I'm gonna tell him.
I'm gonna be strong.
I just called a friend of mine.
Yeah?
I think I may be able to book
The Plaza on short notice.
Really?
The Plaza?
Oh, daddy! Oh, my..
Right. Daddy,
I need to talk to you.
- Please, sit down.
- What is it, sweetie?
There's not gonna be a wedding.
Ross and I are not
getting married.
- What?
- I'm sorry, daddy.
I don't believe this!
Uh.. Daddy, stay calm. Please.
Stay calm? How do you
expect me to stay calm?
This is unacceptable, Rachel.
And I wanna know why?
Is it because that punk Ross
won't marry you?
- That's it. Is that it?
- Yes, yes.
He says I'm damaged goods.
[instrumental music]
So, you, uh, nervous
about getting married?
What are you doing?
Look, let's pretend it's a real
bachelor party, okay?
You know, before your wedding.
It'll be more fun.
Alright.
I can't believe
tomorrow's the big day.
How does it feel
knowin' you're
never gonna be
with another woman again, huh?
Knowing you're gonna have
to wake up to the same face
every day
until you finally have
the sweet release of death.
You're right.
This is more fun.
[knock at door]
That's her.
Okay, come on.
- Hi.
[blows party horn]
So, which one of you
lucky boys is Chandler?
Uh, that-that's me.
That's me.
Joey Tribbiani.
Big fan.
So, is that a bedroom?
Yeah. Yeah, right over there.
Alright, whenever you're ready.
That was weird.
W-why would she
go in the bedroom?
(stripper)
'I'm waiting.'
- So, she's a--
- Yep, that's one naked hooker.
I love your place.
Where's this guy from?
Uh, that's an 18th century
Indian artifact from Calcutta.
- Oh. Wow!
- Yeah.
So...you're more
than just dinosaurs.
- So much more.
- Mm.
[both chuckles]
Oh! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God, I am so sorry.
Uh, forget it.
It's from Pier One.
[knock at door]
Sorry.
You think you can knock up
my daughter
and then not marry her?
I ought to kill you!
You know, this is actually
not a great time for me.
So? Come on!
Explain yourself, Geller.
First, you get
my Rachel pregnant.
You got Rachel pregnant?
- Who did?
- You did!
Yes.
Yes, yes, I did, but-but it was,
it was just a one night thing.
- It meant nothing.
- Oh? Really?
That's what my daughter
means to you? Nothing?
No, no, sir.
Um, she means a lot to me.
I mean, I-I care..
I-I love Rachel.
- What?
- Oh, but not that way. I mean..
I mean,
I'm not in love with her.
I love her like a-like a friend.
Oh, really?
That's how you treat a friend?
You get her in trouble
and then you refuse
to marry her?
Hey, I offered to marry her.
- What?
- But I didn't want to.
Well, why not?
So you could spend
your time with this tramp?
- Tramp?
- Oh, I'm sorry.
Dr. Green, Mona.
Mona, Dr. Green.
I can't believe there
is a naked hooker in there.
Wait, wait, maybe
she's a hooker and a stripper
but she got confused
about what she's supposed to do.
Could be. I mean,
technically, she did strip.
We just, we just missed it.
Ma'am?
Are you also a stripper?
(stripper)
'Uh, no, but I can pretend
to strip.'
'But that's gonna cost extra.'
'Okay, here's the extras.
Handcuffs, spanking..'
Nah-na-ma-huh!
Maybe Monica's playin'
a joke on ya.
You know, gettin'
her own husband a hooker.
That's pretty funny.
That is funny.
Maybe for my birthday,
she'll murder someone.
And I bet Ross
was in on it too.
I mean,
he was conveniently busy.
(stripper)
'Do you mind
if I smoke in here?'
Oh, actually, I'd rather..
[clears throat]
Yeah, go ahead.
We're gonna have to burn
that room down anyway.
How could you have kept
all of this from me?
- I was going to tell you, but--
- But what?
You figured
you'd get what you wanted
then you'd dump her
like you did Rachel.
Hey, I did not dump Rachel.
Nor are we still together.
[telephone ringing]
Oh, um..
Can I..
Why don't we just let
the machine get that?
(Joey on phone)
'Hey, Ross, it's Joey.'
'There's a hooker over here,
and we thought maybe'
'you'd know somethin' about it.'
No, no, no!
No, no! I-I-I need to lie down.
[instrumental music]
So, tonight's the night
of the big bachelor party?
Yeah. Hey, thanks for giving me
that girl's number.
No problem.
So, who's the party for?
Uh, my husband.
You hired your husband a hooker?
- She's a stripper.
- No, she's a hooker.
Is-is that what they call
strippers sometimes?
When they're hookers.
Oh, my God, Stu.
I-I can't believe you did this.
Now, you're absolutely sure
she's a hooker?
Either that
or she's just the best
most expensive date I ever had.
[instrumental music]
Maybe she meant
to get you a hooker.
Why would she do that?
Maybe she wants you
to learn something.
Huh? Now, is there anything
you're really bad at?
You know, sexually?
This is the worst
bachelor party ever.
(stripper)
'What's taking
you boys so long?'
- In a minute.
- In a minute?
What's gonna happen in a minute?
Alright, alright. Maybe..
Maybe you should just ask her
to leave.
- Why me?
- Hey, it's your bachelor party.
Which is why you should do it.
I don't want to.
You do it.
- You do it.
Alright, Rock, Paper, Scissors
for who has to tell
the whore to leave.
- What?
- I miss this.
I don't think we've actually
done this before.
No, no, no.
No, I-I miss
hangin' out with you.
Well, we, we still hang out.
Yeah, but not like we used to.
Remember? You and me
used to be inseparable.
You know, and now it's like..
...things are...different.
Well, you know,
things are different.
I'm, I'm married now.
Yeah, sure.
And hey, don't get me wrong.
I am so happy for you guys.
But I just...I miss..
...hangin' out...just-just us.
You know?
- Yeah, I miss that too.
- Right?
I'll tell you what,
from now on, we'll make time
to hang out with each other.
You got it. Come here.
[chuckles]
Oh, God.
Listen, I am this close
to robbin' you guys.
She's a hooker! She's a hooker!
She's a..
Hi. Uh, we spoke on the phone.
[instrumental music]
So your dad dropped by.
He's a pleasant man.
- Oh, no.
- I better go.
Just over here.
I don't wanna miss the fight.
Ross, I'm so sorry.
Okay, I-I promise,
I will straighten this out
with him tomorrow in person.
Or via e-mail.
I don't care about your dad.
I care about Mona.
She was there and now
she's totally freaked out.
Oh, okay, I'll fix that too.
What's her e-mail address?
Rachel?
Alright, I promise,
I'll fix this. I swear.
I'll-I'll-I'll talk to her.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Okay.
That's it?
You call that a fight? Come on.
"We were on a break."
"No, we weren't."
What happened to you two?
[instrumental music]
[knock at door]
Thank you so much
for coming back over.
Oh, good. You're here.
Yeah, and I was worried that it
was going to be uncomfortable.
I know, Mona,
just hear me out.
First of all, I am so sorry
about my father yelling at you.
But I heard that
you totally held your own.
You're gonna have to tell me
how you did that.
- Focus.
- Okay. Uh, but, okay.
Yes, Ross and I used to date.
And, yes, we are gonna
have...a baby
but we are definitely
not getting back together.
How can I be sure of that?
Oh, because we drove
each other crazy.
- Yeah.
- I mean, he was possessive.
He was jealous. He could never
just let the little things go.
- Trying to date this woman.
- Right.
But none of that
compared to how kind
and, and gentle
and thoughtful he is.
Probably shouldn't touch me.
You know, I-I-I just..
I don't wanna get in the middle
of something so complicated.
I-I get it, but-but, Mona
what relationship
is not complicated?
I mean, we all have our baggage.
You must too.
Why else would you
still be single?
I'm so gonna leave right now.
[sighs]
Should I leave this open
for you too?
I'm not sure yet.
Why didn't you just tell me
about all this?
Because what's going on
with Rachel has nothing to do
with how I feel about you.
Yeah, well, you still
should have told me.
I know, and I was going to
but...I thought it was better
that you heard it
from Rachel's father.
Look, I, I made a mistake.
But it's only 'cause
I really, really like you.
Really.
Okay.
I guess you can...close
the door now.
[knock at door]
Forgot my purse.
Oh. You guys made up.
He's a good kisser, isn't he?
I'm going!
[instrumental music]
I swear I didn't know
she was a hooker.
I mean..
Did you let her smoke in here?
Her ass print is still
on your grandmother's quilt.
Do you really want
to talk about smoking?
You know what?
I'm gonna make this up to you.
I promised you a stripper..
["Let Me Blow Ya Mind"
over stereo]
...and you're gonna
get a stripper.
Monica, wait.
What?
Carry on.
♪ I had to give you up ♪
♪ It's only been a year ♪
♪ I got my foot
through the door ♪
♪ And I ain't going nowhere ♪
♪ It took a while to get me in ♪
♪ And I'm gonna take my time ♪
♪ Don't fight
that good shit.. ♪
Ooh, these tennis shoes
are so tight.
I think I'll take them off.
Could you not narrate?
Gotcha, sailor.
♪ Snakes in my path
wanna smile up at me ♪
♪ They wanna bank up
makes me dizzy ♪
♪ Shank up haters wanna.. ♪♪
(Dr. Green on phone)
'Just because you're not
in love with the guy..'
Oh, you told your dad the truth?
About an hour ago.
- Wanna go see a movie?
- Yes.
Bye, daddy.
(Dr. Green on phone)
'...there's gonna be a wedding!'
'That's unacceptable, Rachel.'
'What the hell does love
have to do with it anyway?'
'There are more important things
in a marriage than love.'
[indistinct chatter
over telephone]
'You have to think about the
consequences of your decision.'
Hey, I do too think
about the consequences
of my decisions.
Well, what gives you
the right to..
Go to hell!
Stupid guy on my phone.
[theme music]